Ah, Hyeon-wu
It hurts, be gentle…
Hey, Hyeong-ju
Hurry up, Hyeong-ju
Okay, I'm coming
Where does he get
that swagger?
Is his hoodie
from a luxury brand?
Should I just ask him?
He helped me
so maybe he'll tell me
Sorry…
I wasn't watching
where I was going
Watch yourself
Okay
That's it
That overflowing
swagger isn't from
his clothes
but from his strength
His indifference
is so cool
The strong never lose
their composure
Be cool, be cool…
Hey, loser
Be cool
Watch yourself
Build up…
a wall of composure
You little…
You punk
I've still got
a long way to go
How do I learn
that swagger?
Wait, I know a way
That's right
A relationship
is important
I have an excuse
to get closer to him
Hey, Hyeon-wu
Could you teach me
some Jiu-Jitsu?